Guide to the Edward S. Harkness, Class of 1897, Yale College, Photograph Collection Documenting Student Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Edward S. Harkness, Class of 1897, Yale College, Photograph Collection Documenting Student life at Yale
1894-1903
RU 670
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The materials consist of photographs of Edward S. Harkness (Yale 1897) depicting Yale scenes, student life, classmates, and various Kappa Psi reunions.
Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 48-A (YRG 48-A), Yale pictorial records and collections.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs of Edward S. Harkness (Yale 1897) depicting Yale scenes, student life, classmates, and various Kappa Psi reunions.
Photographs; Harkness, Edward Stephen, 1874-1940; Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Students
- Photographs, Series I
  - Psi. U., 1896 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kappa Psi, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Freshmen of The Woodbridge, 1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dollars of Dume [?] -Psi. U., 1894 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ponce de Leon -Psi. U., 1895 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football team picture, 1894, 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6 - 7)
  - Class picture, 1897 June (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kappa Psi, Delmonico's, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sexennial, 1903 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - '97 Reunion [sexennial (?) = decennial], undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Charles R. Hemenway; Luther L. Kountze wedding, 1898, n.d (Box 1, Folder 12)